Guide to the Robert Flaherty Film Seminar Archive 1949 - 2011 MSS.326
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Public TV
  - Public Television Seminar 1980 Tape 18, June 6, 1980; ID: 326.1024 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1024)
    Group Evaluation
  - Arden House Evaluation Discussion 1, April 30, 1980; ID: 326.1040 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1040)
  - Arden House Evaluation Discussion 2, April 30, 1980; ID: 326.1041 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1041)
- Series III: Flaherty Israel
  This series contains audio recordings from the 1998 Flaherty Film Seminar in Israel, organized in collaboration with the New Foundation for Cinema and Television, Tel Aviv.
  - Flaherty Israel - Tape 2, 1998; cuid41094 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1025)
  - Flaherty Israel - Tape 3, 1998; cuid41095 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1026)
  - Flaherty Israel - Tape 4, 1998; cuid41096 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1027)
  - Flaherty Israel - Tape 5, 1998; cuid41097 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1028)
    Duration: 92 minutes
  - Flaherty Israel - Tape 6, 1998; cuid41098 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1029)
    Duration: 88 minutes
  - Flaherty Israel - Tape 7, 1998; cuid41099 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1030)
  - Flaherty Israel - Tape 8, 1998; cuid41100 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1031)
  - Flaherty Israel - Tape 9, 1998; cuid41101 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1032)
  - Flaherty Israel - Tape 10, 1998; cuid41102 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1033)
  - Flaherty Israel - Tape 11, 1998; cuid41103 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1034)
  - Flaherty Israel - Tape 12, 1998; cuid41104 (Box 21, Audiocassette ID: 326.1035)
- Series IV: Film Council
  This series contains audio recordings from a 1974 meeting of the Film Council, a group of non profit film exhibition folks: librarians, museums and distributors in NYC, who met once a month to talk about non commercial film.
  - 1974 Film Council Symposium 1, March 23, 1974; ID: 326.1036 (Box 21, Media ID: 326.1036)
    Original Number: N/A
  - 1974 Film Council Symposium 2, March 23, 1974; ID: 326.1037 (Box 21, Media ID: 326.1037)
  - 1974 Film Council Symposium 3, March 23, 1974; ID: 326.1038 (Box 21, Media ID: 326.1038)
  - 1974 Film Council Symposium 4, March 23, 1974; ID: 326.1039 (Box 21, Media ID: 326.1039)
- Series V: Robert Flaherty Recordings and Other Seminar Related Material
  This series contains miscellaneous of audio material from various Film Seminars and activities.
  - "Morning Story" Comock The Eskimo Told by Robery Flaherty - Reel 1 of 2, circa 1949; ID: 326.0001 (Box 1, Media ID: 326.0001, Box Shared Fales 134, Cd 326.0001)
    Duration: Unknown
    Original Number: 2
    Robert Flaherty tells how he came to hear the story of Comock himself.
  - "Morning Story" Comock The Eskimo Told by Robery Flaherty- Reel 2 of 2, circa 1949; ID: 326.0002 (Box 1, Media ID: 326.0002, Box Shared Fales 134, Cd 326.0002)
  - Saturday Night Introductions, 1994; ID: 326.1042 (Box 21, Media ID: 326.1042)
  - Eric Barnouw Nanook Intro., 1994; ID: 326.1043 (Box Shared Fales 045, Media ID: 326.1043)
  - Mani Kaul, 1994; ID: 326.1044 (Box Shared Fales 045, Media ID: 326.1044)
  - Robert Drew, 1994; ID: 326.1045 (Box Shared Fales 045, Media ID: 326.1045)
  - Main Mic Retrospective, 1994; ID: 326.1046 (Box Shared Fales 045, Media ID: 326.1046)
  - Main Mic Retrospective Union Maids, etc., 1994; ID: 326.1047 (Box Shared Fales 045, Media ID: 326.1047)
  - Tiger 1, undated; ID: 326.1048 (Box Shared Fales 045, Media ID: 326.1048)
  - Tiger 2, undated; ID: 326.1049 (Box Shared Fales 045, Media ID: 326.1049)
- Series VI: Seminar and Administrative Papers
  This series contains the paper records of the Robert Flaherty Film Seminar Archive. It consists of packets and brochures handed out at the seminars, programs, press and publicity, planning, grant applications, and all papers pertaining to the daily operations of the organization. The papers have been arranged chronologically by year, and alphabetically within the year. Original folder titles have been maintained where possible.
  - 1946 - 1969 (Box 22)
  - 1970 - 1974 (Box 23)
  - 1974 - 1975 (Box 24)
  - 1976 - 1977 (Box 25)
  - 1978 - 1978 (Box 26)
  - 1979 - 1980 (Box 27)
  - 1980 - 1981 (Box 28)
  - 1981 - 1983 (Box 29)
  - 1983 - 1988 (Box 30)
  - 1989 - 1990 (Box 31)
  - 1990 - 1990 (Box 32)
  - 1990 - 1992 (Box 33)
  - 1993 - 1994 (Box 34)
  - 1994 - 1994 (Box 35)
  - 1995 - 1996 (Box 36)
  - 1996 - 1996 (Box 37)
  - 1996 - 1997 (Box 38)
  - 1997 - 1998 (Box 39)
  - 1998 - 1999 (Box 40)
  - 1999 - 2000 (Box 41)
  - 2000 - 2001 (Box 42)
  - 2001 - 2002 (Box 43)
  - 2002 - 2004; Undated (Box 44)
  - Undated (Box 45)
- Series VII: Financial Papers
  This series contains the financial papers of the Robert Flaherty Film Seminar Archive. It includes budget reports, tax papers, cancelled checks, bills, and all other financial material. The papers have been arranged chronologically by year, and alphabetically within the year. Original folder titles have been maintained where possible.
  - 1959 - 1973 (Box 46)
  - 1973 - 1975 (Box 47)
  - 1976 - 1977 (Box 48)
  - 1977 - 1978 (Box 49)
  - 1978 - 1979 (Box 50)
  - 1980 - 1981 (Box 51)
  - 1981 - 1982 (Box 52)
  - 1983 - 1985 (Box 53)
  - 1986 - 1988 (Box 54)
  - 1988 - 1989 (Box 55)
  - 1989 - 1990 (Box 56)
  - 1990 - 1991 (Box 57)
  - 1991 - 1992 (Box 58)
  - 1993 - 1993 (Box 59)
  - 1993 - 1994 (Box 60)
  - 1995 - 1996 (Box 61)
  - 1996 - 1997 (Box 62)
  - 1997 - 1998 (Box 63)
  - 1998 - 1999 (Box 64)
  - 1999 - 2000 (Box 65)
  - 2000 - 2001 (Box 66)
  - 2001 - 2002 (Box 67)
  - 2002 - 2003 (Box 68)
  - Tax papers, 1963-2003 (Box 69)
- Oversize Series VII: Seminar and Administrative Papers
  - "International Film Seminar Presents: 50 Years of the Flaherty" banner, Undated (Box 72)
  - "Dark Circle" Film poster (2 copies), Undated (Folder 9)